foreign
[Music]
dearest Soul it's been a while since
I've seen you I've been away on a
vacation one that was long overdue
I barely left my home this year so going
on a proper getaway is now a memory I
will cherish forever
[Music]
foreign
and I found a two-room bed and breakfast
hidden away in a forest we've been
putting aside money for a little trip
like this for a while and so fortunate
to get a few rare days off of work
[Music]
foreign
exploring the grounds was a fairy tale
come to life the atmosphere made me feel
as if I was living in a storybook a
little cottage in the woods housing a
lost princess and prince patiently
waiting for a unicorn or other Noble
creature to stop by and impart their
wisdom
foreign
as you can see my imagination ran away
with me and I spent much time
daydreaming but I was with my best
friend and so I was in Kindred company
to enjoy some Whimsical musings by the
lake
[Music]
thank you
foreign
once told me that we each carry a light
of our souls within us but we must
nurture it and polish it so that it
shines
I love that way of seeing things it
appeals to that little girl in my heart
I can feel her sighing and relief happy
to be heard and considered this evening
foreign
to create a little at home Spa just for
fun I felt I'd neglected myself a bit of
late in regards to self-care and even
take a bath which was a treat as I only
have a shower at home
foreign
ly believe that personal care is about a
lot more than taking care of one's
physical self but there was something
healing about brushing out those curly
Tangles long avoided due to stress and
work reminding myself that this too
these slow motions are also important in
their own way
I think anyone who has felt that awful
emptiness of being burned out knows how
difficult it can be to Simply take care
of oneself sometimes
sending my love take care of yourself
and remember to shine your light it is
what will carry you through dark days
and encourage you at your best and above
all it will shine down like moon rays on
those around you and just like that in
such a gentle quiet way you make the
world a little better than a moment
before because you are in it
foreign
[Music]
I hope you all have been having a
wonderful week it has been just
just the best experience you know
getting away for a few days on a
vacation I feel so lucky to have found
this adorable little BNB and it has just
some of the most beautiful area around
it and I've just been enjoying every
minute and it really made me think about
a lot of things and um and gave me a
little bit of break from my work which
made me realize I wanted to make a few
changes in my life going forward and I
think that there's always a lot of power
and to do a little getaway it doesn't
have to be a physical one but at least
mentally you know taking a little bit of
time to seek a new perspective on life
we have for the most part just had our
trip revolve around nature you know we
went to Sol duck Falls which was a
beautiful beautiful area and it took a
little while to get there but we got to
see it along with a lot of other people
and it was just lovely on the way back
we did really enjoy looking through some
antique shops I even went to a tea shop
which was extremely exciting because
they had all the little jars of
different types of teas and spices and
salts available that you could just
smell each one and I had so much fun so
I picked up some jars for my tea over
there one can never have too many jars
we also went into a store and got some
red bandanas for my dog when we come
back home it's going to be hunting
season so it's really important to put
something bright on your dog so that
they're easily noticed when we're
walking through the forest did want to
say a couple things I know every time I
make a video I think since I did a
little interview with my husband there
has been a lot of questions of why he
does not appear in these videos and I
think that the answer will not be
surprising to many he does work full
time time he is a surveyor so it's an
extremely physical job especially out
here you know with so much Wilderness
Area and undeveloped properties he
um you know works really really hard and
often out in a really hot sun or in
extremely cold weather and he's you know
does so much and for him to come home
and me to ask him to be part of my
videos and in a way continue you know
working I think would not be considerate
so that is why he's not in these videos
you know he he does not mind being part
of them now and then one thing I did
want to add is that I know several
people have inquired about my book and
the official release date is the month
of November the kind of date was moving
a little bit because of the printer
trying to have the books already in time
so it is for sure coming out this
November but probably more at the end of
it and a lot of websites have updated
the date accordingly late so yes I do
wish I had more control over the
publishing date but it is just not the
case and it will definitely be coming
out in November and I hope you all
really enjoy it it has been a huge
project and I really appreciate all the
support and I've also been working on a
audiobook version too I'm sending all of
you my love I will let you go before it
gets a little bit too dark the Sun is
setting and tomorrow I have a couple
Adventures planned I really want to find
a pumpkin patch so that is the Big Goal
so I am sending you all my love do take
care of yourselves and I will see you
soon
foreign